{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729825492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729825491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 8e6205ea-748a-4bba-98e9-73bf6dce013f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729831629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729831629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729831973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729831973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729832094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729832094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ni.rand.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729837793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729837792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729842649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729842649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729852007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729852007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729861743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729861743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 938e97cb-3981-4d39-ac42-fb737fdc67fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729879570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729879570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pole-kipi-sasa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sasa"," userResponse":" sasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729888715","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729888713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rosa_zetu-rosa-ubao"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rosa"," userResponse":" rosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729900282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729900282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_kinu-huwa-tisa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729910627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729910627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_babu-lisa-hema"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729921059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729921058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_goso-tisa-osha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729930136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729930136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kisa_kuja-huko-kisa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kisa"," userResponse":" kisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729939745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729939745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_taji-tisa-haki"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729948518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729948518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_bibi-lisa-huko"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729957142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729957142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rosa_rosa-ubao-kaka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rosa"," userResponse":" rosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729965805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729965805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_lake-hawa-hasa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729971709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729971709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_lake-hawa-hasa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729983201","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729983201"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 1f604b46-c71a-47d6-b8b6-ae82cbebbe4a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_lake-hawa-hasa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729995370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729995370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" PALESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549729999890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549729999890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730001460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730001459"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730005386","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730005386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730006965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730006965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730011402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730011402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730013005","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730013005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROSA"," userResponse":" ROSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730016422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730016421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730018527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730018527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730021127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730021127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730027134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730027134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730035727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730035727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730037294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730037294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" LISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730039822","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730039822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" LISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730041398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730041398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730044508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730044508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730046070","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730046070"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730050019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730050018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" START_TISA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730051310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730051310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730052987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730052987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730057524","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730057524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730059534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730059534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730059733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730059732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730065370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730065369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 24f69ee2-7d75-43de-8de4-0c873853cccf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730106604","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730106603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_jike-lisa-humo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730119215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730119215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_hasa-nono-kuoa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730128246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730128245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_naro-hasa-lima"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730146967","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730146967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosa"," userResponse":" kosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730149765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730149765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730161275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730161274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730167588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730167585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730172690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730172689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730178551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730178551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730183735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730183735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" eb731b07-92f0-497c-a7b7-c5d22cebec30"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730220660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730220660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730222856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730222856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730234841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730234841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730241089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730241089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730271494","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730271494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730277976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730277976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730286510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730286509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730294938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730294938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730309589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730309588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730314112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730314112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730326288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730326287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730333171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730333170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730344886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730344886"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730353770","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730353770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730375890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730375890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730381472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730381471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730395645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730395644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730400363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730400362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730456387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730456387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730475089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730475089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730481843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730481842"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730492097","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730492096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730508608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730508607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730520839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730520839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549730523895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549730523895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_193014"," gameId":" 4c096d24-9106-4e36-8edd-2a816fd3f2c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}